newgamenetwork.com 2019-05-05

# Privacy Policy | New Game Network

Last modified: November 28, 2016

* * *

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

_Information Collection_

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address or other details to help you with your experience.

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.

_Cookies_  
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled.

_Log Files_  
New Game Network keeps log files on broad fields to analyze trends, track user movements, and gather data for demographic locations. This is not attached in anyway to visitor's personal identification.

_Contests_  
From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

_Links_  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

_Changes of Privacy Policy_  
Users can be notified of any Privacy Policy changes by visiting this Privacy Policy Page.

Latest Comments

May 2, 2019 by Sasha Kozak  
Great review to one of my all time favorite series! 

Apr 28, 2019 by JamesJay  
Yes, Legends Edition is like the main "gold" version. It... 

Apr 28, 2019 by Kel234  
Can anyone please tell me, in the Legends Edition, do you... 

Apr 27, 2019 by Kat Vic  
It's not going to cost me anymore to pre order. I am... 

Apr 27, 2019 by Jocko Johnson  
not a reason at all, it's manipulating the FOMO effect,...
